https://www.vadirectory.net/terms/

HomeAboutArticlesContact UsTestimonialsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsBecome a VAJoin Our NetworkMember BenefitsMembershipMemLoginMember RenewalCreating websites for new VAsGreat VA ResourcesVAs – Contractor or Employee?What type of VA are you?Post a JobFind a VAAustraliaACTNew South WalesNorthern TerritoryQueenslandSouth AustraliaTasmaniaVictoriaWestern AustraliaBotswanaItalyNew ZealandSpainUnited StatesUnited KingdomVA TrainingACSBlogThe following terms and conditions govern all use of the VADirectory.net website and all content, services, and products available through the website, including, but not limited to, the client area (collectively referred to as the Site). We have a separate Privacy Policy here.This Site is owned and operated by A Clayton’s Secretary, Trading as VA Directory (ABN 76 809 078 624) of PO Box 566, Emerald, Vic, 3782 Australia (“VA Directory”).  This Site is offered subject to your acceptance without modification of all of the terms and conditions contained herein and all other operating rules, policies including, without limitation, the Operator’s privacy policy and procedures that may be published from time to time on this Site by the Operator (collectively, the “Agreement”). This applies across VA Directory, VA Trainer, ACS-Webhosting and ACS WebServices (the “Sites”). When we say ‘we’, ‘us’ or ‘VA Directory’ it’s because that’s who we are and we own and run the above mentioned Sites.Please read this Agreement carefully before accessing or using the Site. By accessing or using any part of the website, you agree to become bound by the terms and conditions of this agreement. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the Site or use any services. The Site is available only to individuals who are at least 18 years old.Client area accountYou are responsible for maintaining the security of your client area account, and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with the account. You must immediately notify the Operator of any unauthorised uses of your account or any other breaches of security. The Operator will not be liable for any acts or omissions by You, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions.Contribution to websiteIf you leave comments anywhere on the Site, post material to the Site, post links on the Site, or otherwise make (or allow any third party to make) material available by means of the Site (any such material, “Content”), You are entirely responsible for the content of, and any harm resulting from, that Content. That is the case regardless of whether the Content in question constitutes text, graphics, audio, or computer software. By making Content available, you represent and warrant that:Downloading, copying and use of the Content will not infringe the proprietary rights, including but not limited to the copyright, patent, trademark or trade secret rights, of any third partyYou have fully complied with any third-party licenses relating to the Content, and have done all things necessary to successfully pass through to end users any required termsThe Content does not contain or install any viruses, worms, malware, trojan horses or other harmful or destructive contentThe Content is not spam, is not machine or randomly generated, and does not contain unethical or unwanted commercial content designed to drive traffic to third party sites or boost the search engine rankings of third party sites, or to further unlawful acts (such as phishing) or mislead recipients as to the source of the material (such as spoofing)The Content is not pornographic, libelous or defamatory, does not contain threats or incite violence towards individuals or entities, and does not violate the privacy or publicity rights of any third partyBy submitting Content to the Operator for inclusion on our Site, you grant the Operator a world-wide, royalty-free, and non-exclusive license to reproduce, modify, adapt and publish the Content for the purpose of displaying, distributing, promoting, marketing or any other lawful use.Without limiting any of those representations or warranties, the Operator has the right (though not the obligation) to, in the Operator’s sole discretion (i) refuse or remove any content that, in the Operator’s reasonable opinion, violates any policy or is in any way harmful or objectionable, or (ii) terminate or deny access to and use of the Site to any individual or entity for any reason, in the Operator’s sole discretion. The Operator will have no obligation to provide a refund of any amounts previously paid under these circumstances.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.We offer the use of an offsite secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) are not stored on our servers.Responsibility of website visitorsBy operating the Site, the Operator does not represent or imply that it endorses any or all of the contributed content, or that it believes such material to be accurate, useful or non-harmful. You are responsible for taking precautions as necessary to protect yourself and your computer systems from viruses, worms, trojan horses, and other harmful or destructive content. The Site may contain content that is offensive, indecent, or otherwise objectionable, as well as content containing technical inaccuracies, typographical mistakes, and other errors. The Operator disclaims any responsibility for any harm resulting from the use by visitors of the Site.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, except to provide products or services you’ve requested. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOur site may contain links to third party sites. These third party sites have separate and independent terms of service and privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.ChangesThe Operator reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this Agreement. It is your responsibility to check this Agreement periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the Site following the posting of any changes to this Agreement constitutes acceptance of those changes. The Operator may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the Site (including, the release of new tools and resources). Such new features and/or services shall be subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.TerminationThe Operator may terminate your access to all or any part of the Site at any time, with or without cause, with or without notice, effective immediately. If you wish to terminate this Agreement you may simply discontinue using the Site. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if you have a client account, such account can only be terminated by the Operator if you materially breach this Agreement and fail to cure such breach within 14 (fourteen) days from the Operator’s notice to you thereof; provided that, the Operator can terminate the Site immediately as part of a general shut down of our service. All provisions of this Agreement which by their nature should survive termination shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.IndemnificationYou agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Operator, its contractors, and its licensors, and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against any and all claims and expenses, including legal fees, arising out of your use of the Site, including but not limited to your violation of this Agreement.Returns and RefundsVA Directory wants its customers and members to be happy with the items they purchase, however we recognise that sometimes there is a genuine need to ask for a refund.We will grant a refund for some items if returned in its original packaging and in resaleable condition.  However, there are some items that cannot be refunded because of the nature of the product. These include:  downloadable files, including audios and ebooks, VA memberships, as well as coaching services.  These items are final sales and non-refundable. Memberships are a minimum 12 month commitment as per the registration page when you sign up.If a refund is due, it will be provided minus any merchant fees, bank charges or other charges incurred as a result of the sale.  The refund will be provided in the same form the original payment was made, i.e. back to your credit card, your Paypal acount or your bank account, or by cheque posted to protect us from any fraudulent activity.This policy also relates to our other sites as mentioned in the first para of this page.  This does not override any guarantees consumers have according to the Australian Consumer Guarantees.Changes to our terms and privacy policiesFrom time to time we may make adjustments to this policy. Changes will be made at our sole discretion. Site’s users are encouraged to check this policy for such changes. Your continued use of this site following changes to this policy constitutes your acceptance of the changes.Contacting usAny questions about these terms of service and privacy policy should be addressed to us via our contact form.This document has been last modified on 22 May 2018. Our most recent posts Whose service are you using for email? Introducing our new Manager Benefits of multiple clientsRead our other postsRead our other postsSelect CategoryAnniversary  (10)Author’s musings  (170)AVAC  (14)Bad business  (25)blog  (3)Blogging  (42)Book Review  (3)Business Networking  (53)Client Ed & Case Studies  (127)Client Interview  (10)COVID-19  (5)Email Etiquette  (34)Facebook  (17)Google+  (1)Healthcare  (14)Instagram  (1)Legalities  (6)LinkedIn  (18)Mistakes VAs make  (89)Networking Tools  (27)Niche  (10)Operating a VA Business  (455)Professional Development  (19)Project 52  (5)Scam Alert  (3)Seasons  (1)Social Media  (2)Technology  (76)Tips & Tricks  (7)Twitter  (10)Uncategorised  (35)Uncategorized  (2)VA Coaching Club  (1)VA Conference  (12)VA Education  (294)VA Industry  (184)VA Stories  (9)Yahoogroups  (3)
NewsletterSignup for news and special offers!
Opt in to receive news and updates.
Subscribe
Thank you!You have successfully joined our subscriber list.
AboutA Clayton’s Secretary T/as VA Directory was established in March 1994 by Kathie M. Thomas.EmailFacebookInstagramLinkedIn
Payment InformationMost of our VAs accept PayPal, major credit cards and/or EFT for payments.Any transactions performed from this site are via a third party SSL server to ensure your privacy.Connect With UsVA Directory PO Box 566 Emerald, Vic, 3782, AustraliaP: +61 437 889 400Terms & ConditionsPlease note: Anyone scraping contact details from our site for the purposes of spamming, adding to lists, etc, will be reported.Powered by WishList Member - Membership Software
